national-lottery.com 2015-03-17

# National-Lottery.com Privacy Statement

Your privacy is extremely important to us and our Privacy Policy ensures that any information provided to us is used and protected in an ethical and secure manner.

## Cookies

The only information collected by National-Lottery.com comes from industry-standard cookies that you can choose to accept or reject via the preferences settings on your computer. Cookies are a normal part of website browsing and play an important role in helping websites optimising your browsing experience by providing information which is of most interest to you.

The cookies used by National-Lottery.com tell us which pages people visit on our site and how long they spend on each page. We collect data to find out what you do and don’t like so we can work towards providing more of the information you want. This allows us to constantly improve our website by offering information which is of most interest to our readers.

It is important to note that cookies do not grant us access to your computer or to any information about you as an individual – only to the limited amount of data that you have agreed to share with us for the purposes previously described. For this reason, the default settings on most web browsers accept cookies automatically. You can, of course, adjust your web browser settings to decline cookies, but you should be aware that doing this could make websites less intuitive.

## Links

Like most websites, National-Lottery.com contains links to third party websites which we think may be of interest to you. However, this Privacy Policy only pertains to National-Lottery.com and other websites you choose to visit via our links may have different data and privacy policies. We advise users look at the privacy policy of any third-party website as we cannot be held responsible for how those websites collect and use data.

## Security

Your privacy and security is one of our top priorities, so we work hard to make sure that your personal information cannot be accessed by unauthorised persons. Steps taken to maintain the highest levels of security include physical protection of all hardware, implementation of electronic security protocols and, of course, the strictest managerial oversight.
